Joseph Digoro

City of Tshwane, Gauteng, South Africa



digorojoseph@gmail.com



0609606081



linkedin.com/in/joseph-digoro-b15913a3

Summary

Experienced Full Stack Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Computer Literacy, Communication, Decision-Making, Presentation Skills, and Problem Solving. Strong engineering professional with a National Diploma in Software Development focused in Information Technology from Tshwane University of Technology.

Experience



Junior Developer

Absa Group

Jun 2022 - Present (3 months +)

Frontend development

Full-stack Developer

The Digital Academy

Dec 2021 - Present (9 months +)

- Creating Frontend Applications using Angular, Ionic, HTML, CSS and TypeScript.
- Creating Backend Applications and REST API using Express JS, Node JS and JavaScript.
- Testing APIs using Postman and Thunder client.
- Creating and maintaining databases using PG Admin (PostgreSQL) and Mongoose (MongoDB).
- Designing wireframes using Figma.
- Designing and creating UML diagrams using Draw IO.
- Tracking & managing tasks using Trello and Gitlab issues.
- Colleborating with teams using Gitlab and Githab.
- · Performing daily Stand ups on Discord.

Stockroom Merchandiser

JAM Clothing SA

May 2016 - Jan 2018 (1 year 9 months)

- · Recieving deliveries
- Checking consignments
- · Capturing stock in the system

Store Associate

JAM Clothing SA

Dec 2014 - May 2016 (1 year 6 months)

- Stock packing
- Merchandising
- Customer service

Cashier

Education



Tshwane University of Technology

National Diploma in Software Development, Information Technology

Jan 2018 - Aug 2021

- Database Design and Implementation
- · System Analysis and Design
- C++ procedural and Object Oriented programming
- Linux bash
- · Comptia A+
- Cisco Networking
- Project Management
- Information System
- Oracle SQL & PL/SQL
- Computer Literacy
- Computer Fundamentals

Licenses & Certifications



CCNA: Introduction to Networks - Cisco

The Complete Java Developer Course - Mastering Java from Zero - Udemy

Skills

Ionic Framework • PostgreSQL • MongoDB • Express.js • Node.js • Communication • Trello • Git BASH • Decision-Making • Problem Solving